<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text</string>
    <string name="article_title">Beatles Anthonology Vol.1</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">Behind That Locked Door: Beatles rarities!</string>
    <string name="article_text">In a vault deep inside Abbey Road Studios in London - protected by an unmarked, triple-locked, police-alarmed door- are something like 400 hours of unreleased Beatles recordings, starting from June 2, 1962 and ending with the very last tracks recorded for the Let It Be album. The best of the best were released by Apple Records in the form of the 3 volume Anthology series.
        For more information, see the Beatles Time Capsule at www.rockument.com
        \n\n
        This volume starts with the first new Beatle song, &quot;Free as a Bird&quot; (based on a John Lennon demo, found only on The Lost Lennon Tapes Vol 28, and covers the very earliest historical recordings, outtakes from the first albums, and live recordings from early concerts and BBC Radio sessions.
        \n\n
        <b>Highlights include:</b>
        \n\n
        <b><i>Cry for a Shadow</i></b> - Many a Beatle fanatic started down the outtake road, like I did, with a first listen to this song. Originally tited Bestle Bop&quot; and recorded in a single session that yielded four songs (the other three featured Tony Sheridan with the Beatles as a backing band) &quot;Cry for a Shadow&quot; is an Instrumental written by Lennon and Harrison, which makes it
        unique to this day. John Lennon Plays rhythm guitar, George attend by the Queen. "Till There Was You"
        (by Meredith Wilson) is from the musical The Music Man and a hit for Peggy Lee in 1961. Before playing it, Paul said it was recorded by his
        fovorite American group. "Sophie Tucker" (which got same laught). At the end, John tells the people in the cheapter seats to clap their hands, and the rest to "rattle your jewelry" and then announces "Twist and Shout" (a song by Bert Rusell and Phil Medley that was first recorded in 1978).
        A film of the performance shows the Queen smiling at John's remaks.

    </string>
</resources>